http://www.sivallighting.com/privacy-policy

C7 & C9 Light Strings
C7 Light Strings & SpoolsC9 Light String & SpoolsC7 & C9 Magnetic Spools
Commercial Grade Light Strings
Candelabra Base (E12)Intermediate Base (E17)Medium Base (E26/E27)
Party & Events Bulbs
S14 "Bistro", A15, A19 (Medium Base) Party Light BulbsGlobe (G30, G40, G50) Light BulbsAntique Edison Light BulbsLED Party BulbsSign Light Bulbs
Lighting Sets/Kits
Commercial Grade String Light KitsGlobe String Light KitsPre-Assembled Candelabra Globe Light Sets
Accessories
Steel Cable (Guy Wire) & Zip TiesPlugs & SocketsDimmers, Extension Cords & Plain WireMounting ClipsCo-Axial Cords & Splitters
New ProductsWholesale
We will be closed for our Annual Shutdown starting December 22 - January 4, 2021. We will open again on January 5, 2021. Our last day to ship will be Monday, December 21, 2020.
Order Online or Call Us @ 1-800-777-8667
HomeHoliday C7/C9 Bulbs
LED C7/ C9 Christmas Replacement BulbsC7/C9 Christmas Bulbs
Holiday Mini Lights
MinilightsLED Light StringsIcicle & Net Lights
C7 & C9 Light Strings
C7 Light Strings & SpoolsC9 Light String & SpoolsC7 & C9 Magnetic Spools
Commercial Grade Light Strings
Candelabra Base (E12)Intermediate Base (E17)Medium Base (E26/E27)
Party & Events Bulbs
S14 "Bistro", A15, A19 (Medium Base) Party Light Bulbs
S14, A15, A19 Party Light Bulbs (Incandescent)LED S14 Party "Bistro" Bulbs
Globe (G30, G40, G50) Light Bulbs
G30, G40 & G50 Globe Bulbs - Candelabra (E12) BaseG30, G40 & G50 Globe Bulbs - Intermediate (E17) BaseG50 Globe Bulbs - Medium (E26/E27) BaseLED Globe (G30, G40. G50) Party Light Bulbs
Antique Edison Light Bulbs
LED Antique Edison Light BulbsIncandescent Antique Edison Light Bulbs
LED Party Bulbs
LED S14 "Bistro" Party BulbsLED Globe (G30, G40, G50) Light BulbsLED Filament BulbsLED Premium BulbsLED Professional Grade BulbsLED Constellation BulbsLED Fairy Globe Bulbs
Sign Light Bulbs
Lighting Sets/Kits
Commercial Grade String Light KitsGlobe String Light KitsPre-Assembled Candelabra Globe Light Sets
Accessories
Steel Cable (Guy Wire) & Zip TiesPlugs & SocketsDimmers, Extension Cords & Plain WireMounting ClipsCo-Axial Cords & Splitters
Wholesale
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.sival.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following: What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. Your Access to and Control Over Information  You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website: See what data we have about you, if any. Change/correct any data we have about you. Have us delete any data we have about you. Express any concern you have about our use of your data. Security  We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.  While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. Updates Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
Categories
Christmas Lighting
Party, Wedding, & Backyard Lighting
Outdoor Light Strings
Lighting Sets/Kits
Customer Service
Wholesale Ordering Policies
Shipping
Copyright © 2019 - Sival, Inc. - All Rights Reserved
Sival, Inc  ~ Established 19853350 Scott Blvd, Bldg 23 Santa Clara, CA 95054PHONE:    1-800-777-8667 or 1-408-492-1391 | FAX:   1-408-492-1393 |  HOURS:    M-F 8:30AM - 5:00PM PST | EMAIL:   sales@sival.com
We may use cookies to enhance your visit with us. By using our website you agree to our use of these cookies.
Please wait
